I'm Peppa Pig. Oink!
-This is my little brother George.
-Oink, oink!
This is Mommy Pig. Oink!
And this is Daddy Pig. Oink!
[laughing]
Peppa Pig. Oink!
Gym Class.
[horn honks]
[narrator] Peppa and her friends
are going to the gym today.
Let's check
you've all got your gym kits on.
[narrator]
Pedro is wearing a superhero costume.
Pedro, where is your gym kit?
It's at home.
I thought it was dressing-up day.
Follow me, children.
[narrator] This is the gym,
where mommies and daddies come
to exercise and enjoy themselves.
Are you all having fun?
Yes, lots of fun.
Your gym teacher for today
is Grampy Rabbit.
Where is he?
Hello, children.
Are you ready to exercise?
Yes, Grampy Rabbit.
[yells]
Do we have to do that?
No, that's only for big athletes like me.
Not for little explorers like you.
We're not explorers.
I'll make explorers of you.
But you. You look like a super hero.
Uh... It's just pretend.
Pretending, that's good.
Right, let's warm up.
Everyone, run on the spot.
[laughing]
And flap your arms.
Now, stretch, stretch.
Wobble like a jelly.
[burbling]
[all laughing, then burbling]
And... rest.
Now we're all warmed up. We can start.
-Start what?
-Your adventure.
I want you to pretend
that this room is a jungle.
It doesn't look like a jungle.
-Where are the trees?
-You have to imagine it.
The trees, the rain,
the fast flowing river at your feet.
Your first adventure is to walk
on this beam, across the river.
Oh! That's easy.
Ah! But it's night time, and it's windy.
[imitates wind blowing]
What?
That's how it was for me.
It was a dark and stormy night.
I was on an adventure.
Ready?
[bleats] But it's not windy or night time.
You have to pretend.
[narrator]
Everyone crosses the pretend river safely.
Hooray!
Well done, my little explorers.
What's next, Grampy Rabbit?
Your next adventure is to swing across
this swamp full of crocodiles.
[in unison] Ah!
I can't see any crocodiles.
You've got to pretend.
Let those crocodiles know who's boss.
Go away, you naughty crocodiles.
That's the spirit.
Did you ever swing across
a crocodile swamp?
Of course I did.
Were you scared?
Not as scared as they were of me.
[yells]
Ready? Don't forget to do the call.
[all yelling]
[narrator] Everyone has crossed
the pretend crocodile swamp safely.
Well done.
What's our next adventure?
This is a vault.
Big athletes jump over it, like this.
Ooh!
But you can pretend it's a dinosaur
and crawl through its legs.
Have you crawled through
a dinosaur's legs, Grampy Rabbit?
Oh, yes.
Once, I was walking in the jungle,
when I stumbled
into a lost world of dinosaurs.
[roars]
[giggling]
And that's it.
You've made it out of the jungle.
Hooray!
Ah-ho!
Did you have a good gym class, children?
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
They're real little explorers now.
We walked across a river.
And we swung over crocodiles.
And we crawled under a dinosaur.
I love doing Gym Class
with Grampy Rabbit. Oink!
[Peppa] The Blackberry Bush.
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are at Granny and Grandpa Pig's house.
Oink. Today I'm going to make
apple and blackberry crumble.
Yummy.
I need you brave explorers
to go and get the fruit.
Aye, aye, Granny Pig.
-We've got baskets for the apples.
-And buckets for the blackberries.
Oink. First, the easy bit, picking apples.
On the count of three, shake the tree.
One, two, three.
[giggling]
-Now for the blackberries.
-Why don't we just have apple crumble?
Because blackberries are tasty, too,
Grandpa.
Okay.
Now the hard bit.
Now, that's what I call a blackberry bush.
This bush has been here
since I was a little piggy.
Oink. It's an overgrown weed.
I should have cut it down years ago.
Grandpa, why don't you like it?
I don't like the way it looks at me.
Silly Grandpa. It's just a harmless bush.
And it's covered in lovely blackberries.
[narrator] George has seen
some really big juicy blackberries.
[whines]
Careful, George, or you might get tangled.
[giggles]
I have a stick
for picking hard-to-reach blackberries.
Clever Grandpa.
But the best blackberries
are right at the very top.
That's why I've brought the ladder.
Um... Don't lean too far over, Mommy Pig.
Don't worry. I've been climbing this
blackberry bush since I was a little girl.
-Yes, but you're not a little girl now.
-I know what I'm doing.
[screams]
[narrator] Oh, dear. Mommy Pig has fallen
into the blackberry bush.
Mommy, can you get out?
No. I'm stuck.
You're stuck in a thorny bush
like Sleeping Beauty.
What?
Once upon a time, there was a princess
called Sleeping Beauty.
One day she fell asleep in a thorny bush,
and she stayed there for a hundred years.
Yes, that's a nice story, Peppa.
[bell chimes]
[narrator] It is Suzy Sheep.
-[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
-Oink. Hello, Suzy.
My mommy is in a blackberry bush.
And she'll be there for a hundred years.
Like Sleeping Beauty. [laughs]
And she'll be rescued by a handsome prince
who will give her a kiss.
[giggles] My mommy is having an adventure.
I wish my mommy
would have adventures like that.
Um... Can someone think of a way
to get me out of here?
Don't worry, Mommy.
In a hundred years,
a handsome prince will rescue you.
Oink. I'll be that handsome prince.
Grandpa Pig, may I borrow
your pruning shears, please?
Of course you may,
brave Sir Daddy Pig.
Stand back, everyone.
Take that, you thorny bush, you.
-Yay!
-Aw...
-My prince.
-My princess.
Mmmwah!
You were meant to stay in there
for a hundred years.
That was quite long enough, thank you.
Oink. Mommy is a blackberry bush.
I thought this sort of thing
only happened to me.
Oink! Stand still while we pick you.
[children giggling]
Let's take all this fruit
back to Granny Pig.
Granny. Granny.
Mommy had an adventure.
And then Mommy fell in the bush.
She looked quite silly.
And she was going: Ah!
"Help me. Help me."
And then Daddy came and rescued her.
The end.
Thank you, Peppa.
I think we've all heard that story
enough times now.
But it's funny.
I never want to see
another blackberry in my life.
So, you don't want any
apple and blackberry crumble?
Well...
Mmm!
Delicious.
[narrator] Mummy Pig loves
apple and blackberry crumble.
Everyone loves
Apple and blackberry crumble.
[Peppa] Pottery.
[narrator] Peppa and George are playing
at Zoe Zebra's house.
Little Zuzu and Zaza
are making a jungle with play-clay.
George has made a dinosaur
out of play-clay.
Grr!
Peppa and Zoë are having a dolls' picnic.
Hello, Mr. Monkey.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Monkey says yes.
What's the magic word, Mr. Monkey?
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
That means "please."
Oh, we haven't got a tea set.
We could make a tea set out of play-clay.
[Peppa] Yes.
George, can we use the play-clay, please?
No. Grr!
Zuzu, Zaza, we need to make a tea set
for our tea party.
-No.
You can help us make it.
[giggling]
I'll make the teapot.
And we'll make the cups.
There. Now Monkey can have tea.
Oh, this teapot is too soft.
Real tea sets aren't soft.
My mommy makes real pots.
-She does pottery.
-Ooh!
Mommy.
Can you help us make a tea set, please?
With tea cups and a teapot
that we can put real water in.
Okay. Come with me.
[announcer] This is where Mrs. Zebra
makes her pottery.
Let's make this tea set.
-Oink. What's that?
-Clay.
All pottery starts off like that.
But it's soft, like play-clay.
We need it to be soft so we can shape it.
But later, it won't be soft.
Ooh!
[narrator] Mommy Zebra is making
a little cup on the potter's wheel.
-There. One cup.
-Wow!
Oink. That looks easy.
-Would you like to try?
-Yes, please.
[giggles] It's all slimy.
Ah! It's all gone wrong.
[narrator] Making a cup
on a potter's wheel is not easy.
There is an easier way to make a cup.
First we roll the clay
into a long worm, like this.
Oink. It's a wiggly worm.
♪ I'm a wiggly worm
I'm a wiggly worm ♪
♪ I'm made of clay
What shall I make today? ♪
♪ I'm a wiggly worm ♪
[Mrs. Zebra]
We wrap it round and round like this.
It's a bit bumpy.
Now I smooth it out with my hands.
-And I add a handle.
-[giggles]
It's a cup.
Now we have two cups.
Yes. But a tea set needs
more than two cups.
-We'll all make cups.
-Yes.
[giggling]
Dinosaur.
George has made a dinosaur.
George always makes dinosaurs.
-Grr!
-Oh, what a scary dinosaur.
Now we need to bake the tea set in a kiln.
[narrator] A kiln is an oven
that cooks the clay and makes it hard.
[chimes]
-The tea set should be ready now.
-Hooray!
Now we paint them.
[narrator] The children are painting
the tea set lovely bright colors.
The tea set is finished.
Now we can have our tea party.
There's a cup for everyone.
Oh, we forgot to make a teapot.
I know. George's dinosaur
can be the teapot.
Yes. Let's fill it with water.
[giggles]
This is the best tea set in the world.
Everybody knows
that all the finest tea sets
have a dinosaur in them.
Teapot. Grr!
[Peppa] Paper Airplanes.
[narrator]
Daddy Pig is getting ready to go to work.
Good. That's all the papers I need. Bye.
Bye-bye, Daddy.
Mommy, can we make something?
-Yes. What would you like to make?
-Dinosaur.
Oh, George.
You always say "dinosaur" for everything.
Let's make an airplane.
-Oink, oink!
-[narrator] George likes airplanes.
Can we make an airplane that flies?
-Yes. All we need is some paper.
-Oink!
We know where there's paper.
[giggling]
[narrator] There is lots of old paper
in the workroom.
-Here's some paper.
-Perfect.
[narrator] Mummy Pig is going
to make a paper airplane.
[Mommy Pig]
Fold the paper down the middle.
Now fold the corners in at one end.
Fold those corners in again
to make a point.
Then fold the sides back like this.
Oink! Paper airplanes.
[imitates plane engine]
Let's see if they can fly.
-Oink!
-Oink, oink!
Ready, steady, go.
[both] Ooh!
[narrator] Mommy Pig's airplane
has flown into a tree.
My turn. Wee!
[narrator] Peppa's airplane has landed
in a flowerpot.
-Your turn, George.
-Wee!
[narrator] George's airplane is doing
a loop the loop.
-And has landed in the duck pond.
-[quacking]
-[giggles]
-Let's make a big airplane.
We'll need a really big piece of paper.
Here's a big piece of blue paper.
[narrator] Peppa and George
have made a big blue airplane.
[horn honks]
Daddy Pig.
-Oink. Hello, everyone.
-Shouldn't you be at work?
Yes, but I've forgotten
some important papers.
Daddy, we're making airplanes.
Oink. We made a really big one.
Wow! Fantastic.
You need someone big and strong
to throw it.
-Ready, steady, go.
-Go!
[narrator] The big blue airplane is flying
very high and very far.
-It just keeps on going.
-Bye-bye, airplane.
[laughs]
Bye-bye.
Now, I need to find
my important work papers.
Has anyone seen any pieces of paper?
-Um...
-Uh...
Maybe you should follow me.
-Is this one of your important papers?
-Yes. That's one of them.
Is this one of your important papers,
Daddy?
Yes. Thank you, Peppa.
[duck quacks]
-Uh... Why are we at the duck pond?
-[quacks]
Oh, I see.
-Thank you, Mrs. Duck.
-[quacks]
The only paper I'm missing now
is a big blueprint.
Hmm... Is it big and blue?
Like the airplane you threw
a long way away, Daddy?
Oh... Um...
The one that we said bye-bye to?
Yes. Maybe I should ring the office.
[phone beeps, then line ringing]
[narrator] This is Daddy Pig's office.
[ringing continues]
Hello, Daddy Pig.
Did you find the papers?
I found some of them.
The only one we need is the big blueprint.
-That might be a problem.
-Daddy threw it away.
-Threw it away?
-[Peppa] And it flew and flew forever.
[yelps]
It's here. It just landed on my desk.
Eh?
What a great idea
to make it into a paper airplane
and throw it to us.
Oh, yes, welI, I am a bit of an expert
at throwing things.
Thank you, Daddy Pig.
[narrator] Now the blueprint is delivered,
Daddy Pig can take
the rest of the day off work.
[sighs]
That's nice.
Daddy, we need your newspaper.
-Oink. What for?
-Making paper airplanes.
[laughing]